Duy Nguyen Tuong

Software Developer

Info

Address

Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Phone

+84 354 265 303

Email

duy.pateo@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

12-12-1995 Binh Dinh, Vietnam

Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

PHP

MySQL

AJAX

Python

Bootstrap

Foundation

LESS

jQuery

Vue JS

Git

Underscore JS

Languages

Vietnamese

Native

English Intermediate

Profile

I'm Duy and I'm a software developer. I have experienced in Web developement technologies. In my mind, programing languages are tools and the most important things are programing logic thinking, problem solving, organization and management skills that I want to improve in my career opportunities.

Employment History

Front-end Developer (Partime), FHH Startup

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017 Go Vap District, Ho Chi Minh City

- Work on Website Front-end development (HTLM/CSS/JS)
- Create website templates as customer request
- Mobile responsive
- Organizes projects with team via Trello
- Use GIT for versioning control
- · Integrate with Back-end by Python
- · Work on Landing page builder project that let user create landing page by themselves
- Frameworks and Libraries: Python Flask, Jinja Template, CSS Foundation Framwork, jQuery, jQuery UI

Front-end Developer (Freelancer), Tim Viec Nhanh

Jan 2018 - Feb 2018 Ho Chi Minh City

- Convert PSD to HTML/CSS
- Use Javascript to handle user events on template

Back-end Developer (Partime), OPPO Vietnam

Mar 2018 - Jul 2018 LIM II Tower, District 3, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Maintaince and develope ERP System
- Collaborate with other team (Marketing, Accounting, Sale Admin, Trade) for handle business logic in ERP System
- Design database and backend for new Marketing Campaign Websites
- Research and build mobile application from Website technologies like Adobe PhoneGap, Apache Cordova, PWA(Progressive Web Application)
- Use SVN for version control
- Frameworks and Libraries: Zend PHP Framework, Phalcon PHP Framework

Hobbies

Listening to music, Watching movie, Reading, Running, Traveling, Videography, Drink Coffee

Full stack Developer, B2BE Vietnam

Jul 2018 - Present Loyal Building, District 3, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Work on EDI system and highly configurable B2B software
- Experience with web API and web services
- Take part in full software development lifecycle (SDLC) which includes user requirement analysis, designing and writing new software programs, testing and final deployment of the allocated projects
- Work individually as well as within the team to deliver and maintain projects as well as provide product support to others
- Work closely with other functional teams in different geographical regions to ensure successful delivery of customer
- Ensure on-going development practices for consistency, reliability, performance and continuity
- Frameworks and libraries: MySQL, Code Igniter PHP Framework, Composer, Underscore JS library, jQuery library, Vue JS, Webpack

Education

Ho Chi Minh University of Transport, Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology

Sep 2014 – Aug 2018 Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Computer Skills
- Data Structure and Algorithm
- Computer Architecture
- Oriented Object Programming
- Database Management System
- Mobile Programing
- Web Development
- Java Programing
- · System Analysis and Design
- Human-Computer Interaction
- Network: Programming, Management, Security, Wireless
- Software Quality Assurance